Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings File, 1969-2014 and undated; 7
  - 2013, 8
    - 9/23--Agency size/mergers, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - 9/23--Rosewood Hotels, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - 9/23-25--Advertising Week, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - 9/25-26--Advertising Week, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - 9/26-27--Advertising Week, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - 9/30--Interbrand, 2013; 2 folders (Box 167, Folder 8-9)
    - 9/30--Maxwell House, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - 10/3--Meredith/Scripps Networks Interactive, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - 10/7--ANA Masters of Marketing, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - 10/8--ANA Masters of Marketing, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - 10/10--Center for Investigative Reporting, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - 10/11--CVS, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - 10/14--Glad Food Protection, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - 10/14--Public relations, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - 10/16--Honey and imports, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - 10/18--Halloween, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - 10/21--Manischewitz and Thanksgiving, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - 10/21--Premium Outlets/Christmas, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - 10/22--Infinit/Campfire, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - 10/30--L'Oreal, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - 11/4--Month of MozArt, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - 11/4--Playbill, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - 11/7--Care Package campaign, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - 11/11-13--Del Monte Nature's Recipe, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - 11/12--Horizon Media/Scout Wellness, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - 11/13--Research in Motion/Blackberry, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - 11/15--Christmas, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - 11/18--Seattle Office of Film and Music, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - 11/19--ABC/Target, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - 11/20--JFK assassination 50th anniversary, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - 11/25--Arts Brookfield, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - 11/25--Shazam/Aha (music in ads), 2013 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - 11/26--Michael Duda/Johannes Leonardo, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - 11/29--20 Questions, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - 11/30--Blackberry, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - 12/1--Bud Light "Hold My Beer" videos, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - 12/1--Principle 6 campaign (Olympics, anti-gay protest), 2013 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - 12/2--New Amsterdam vodka, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - 12/3--Art Basel, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - 12/3--Turkish Airlines, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - 12/4--Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - 12/5--Native advertising/Content marketing, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - 12/6--Grammy's, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - 12/9--Bridges Academy, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - 12/9--WPP, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - 12/10--ACLU/My Big Gay (Il)legal Wedding, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - 12/12--Zeus Jones, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - 12/13--Vanity Fair/Hennessy, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - 12/16--Schneider Electric, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - 12/24--Kiehl's "Keep a Child Alive", 2013 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Olympics/Gay activism, 2013 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl, 2013; 2 folders (Box 171, Folder 11-12)
    - Super Bowl, 2013; 3 folders (Box 172, Folder 1-3)
    - Super Bowl--Audi, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Axe Apollo, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Beck's Sapphire, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Best Buy, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--Blackberry, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--Bud Light, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--Budweiser, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--Budweiser Black Crown, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--Calvin Klein, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Cars.com, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--Century 21, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Chrysler, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--Coca-Cola, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--Doritos, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--E*Trade, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--Gildan, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--GoDaddy.com, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 21)
    - Super Bowl--Kia, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 22)
    - Super Bowl--Lincoln, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 23)
    - Super Bowl--M, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 24)
    - Super Bowl--Mennen Speedstick, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 25)
    - Super Bowl--Mercedes, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 26)
    - Super Bowl--Milk, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 27)
    - Super Bowl--Oreos, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 28)
    - Super Bowl--Paramount, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 29)
    - Super Bowl--Pepsi Next, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 30)
    - Super Bowl--Samsung Mobile, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 31)
    - Super Bowl--Skechers, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 32)
    - Super Bowl--Sodastream, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 33)
    - Super Bowl--Subway, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 34)
    - Super Bowl--Taco Bell, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 35)
    - Super Bowl--Tide, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 36)
    - Super Bowl--Toyota, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 37)
    - Super Bowl--VW, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 38)
    - Super Bowl--Wonderful, 2013 (Box 172, Folder 39)
  - 2014, 9
    - 1/6--Activia, 2014 (Box 172, Folder 40)
    - 1/6--Advertising Age print frequency cutback, 2014 (Box 172, Folder 41)
    - 1/8--Jeffrey Group/Pinta (Hispanic marketing), 2014 (Box 172, Folder 42)
    - 1/8--MDC Partners/Luntz Global, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - 1/10--SodaStream Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - 1/10--YouTube/Sundance, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - 1/13--BBDO/Visa, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - 1/14--Jaguar Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - 1/15--Anheuser-Busch Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - 1/16--Side Project project, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - 1/17--Super Bowl YouTube Adblitz, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - 1/21--Chobani Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - 1/21--Urban Ministries of Durham (N.C.) Names for Change campaign, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - 1/22-23--Timex, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - 1/23--H, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - 1/24--Grammy's, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - 1/27--Brooks Running "Come Fly With Me", 2014 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - 1/27--Squarespace Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - 1/28--Olympics/#cheerstoSochi protest hijack/Queer Nation NY, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - 1/29--Cheerios diversity spot, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - 1/30--AXA Equitable, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - 1/31--Super Bowl ad preview, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - 2--Olympics, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - 2/3--Clearwater Fla., 2014 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - 2/4--AT, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - 2/4--Budweiser "Puppy Love", 2014 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - 2/5--The Real (series), 2014 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - 2/7--Metropolitan Transportation Authority/Korey Kay, 2014 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - 2/7--Olympics ad preview, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - 2/10--HSS (Hospital for Special Surgery), 2014 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - 2/12--Barbie swimsuit, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - 2/13--PETA/VW, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - 2/18--Atlantic 10 Conference, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - 2/19--Miller Fortune beer, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - 2/21--Banana Republic/Same-sex couples, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - 2/24--CBS Watch! Magazine, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - 2/25--VF Social Club, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - 2/26--Hotels.com, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - 2/27--El Rey Network, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - 3/3--Chips Ahoy, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - 3/3--H, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - 3/4--Oscars, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - 3/5--Weather Channel upfront, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - 3/7--NBCUniversal/NBC upfront, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - 3/7--United Nations He for She campaign, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - 3/10--JWT 150th anniversary, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - 3/10--Stone Arch Creative, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - 3/11--ConAgra/P, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - 3/12--The One Show, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - 3/13--MWW/Macias Media (LGBT marketing), 2014 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - 3/13--WGN America, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - 3/17--Hallmark/Nickelodeon, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - 3/26--TV Land Live, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - 3/27--E! upfront, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - 3/28--Digitaria/JWT, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - 3/31--Major League Baseball, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - 3/31--National Peanut Board, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - 4/1--April Fools on Madison Avenue, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - 4/2--Ikea, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - 4/3--TV upfronts, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - 4/7--Vita Coco Kids, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - 4/7--Discovery Channel upfront, 2014 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - 4/8--NBC, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - 4/8--Oxygen/Bravo upfront, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - 4/9--AT, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - 4/9--Hearst magazines, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - 4/11--Mad Men season 7, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - 4/13--Betabrand/Education Life, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - 4/14--JWT rebranding, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - 4/14--Maxwell House, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - 4/14--Mizuno, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - 4/16--Coined words, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - 4/16--Pivot upfront, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - 4/21--Interpublic Group, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - 4/28--South Nevada Water Authority, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - 4/29--Digital Content Newfronts, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - 4/30--Digital Content Newfronts, 2014 (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - 5/1--Digital Content Newfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - 5/2--Digital Content Newfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - 5/3--Digital Content Newfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - 5/5--New Yorker Festival, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - 5/6--Digital Content Newfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - 5/7--Diet Coke, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - 5/12--TV Upfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - 5/13--TV Upfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - 5/14--TV Upfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - 5/15--TV Upfronts, 2014 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - 5/15--TV Upfronts, 2014; 2 folders (Box 180, Folder 1-2)
    - 5/16--TV Upfronts, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - 5/19--AFAR Collection, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - 5/19--TV Upfronts, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - 5/22--ANA/Brand Activation Association, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - 5/27--Briggs Riley, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - 5/27--Dairy Queen, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - 5/29--Ritz-Carlton, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - 5/30--Three Lions/Movies Rock, 2014 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - 5/30--TV upfronts, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - 5/31--Cheerios, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - 6/2--AKQA, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - 6/2--Negroni Week, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - 6/3--Subway web series, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - 6/4--AMEX documentary, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - 6/5--TV Upfronts, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - 6/5--World Cup, 2014; 3 folders (Box 181, Folder 8-10)
    - 6/9--Kirshenbaum Bond Senecal, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - 6/9--Vanity Fair/Born Curious, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - 6/10--Autotrader.com, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - 6/12--RTB 500 Index, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - 6/13--Nationwide, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - 6/16--Barclay/Noise, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - 6/20--Creative for Good, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - 6/23--Le Meridien Hotels, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - 6/24--Goodby Silverstein/Dali Museum, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - 6/30--Levi Strauss, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - 7--Procter Gamble, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - 7/1--Wheaties, 2014 (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - 7/2--GoDaddy, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - 7/7--Los Angeles Zoo, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - 7/7--USA summer promos, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - 7/8--Farmland Bacon, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - 7/9--Joel McHale/Purity Vodka, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - 7/11--Young Rubicam/Inspire, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - 7/14--AARP television show, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - 7/14--ThinkThin, 2014 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - 7/15--World Cup, 2014; 2 folders (Box 183, Folder 9-10)
    - 7/16--Pfizer, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - 7/17--Heineken/Neil Patrick Harris, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - 7/21--Back to school shopping, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - 7/21-29--Tennessee Music/Tourism, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - 8/14--JC Penney/Liz Claiborne, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - 8/15--Lauren Bacall, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - 8/18--Edelman, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - 8/18--Okocat, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - 8/19--CBS/Football, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - 8/20--California Milk Board, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - 8/21--MTV Music Video Awards, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - 8/22--NASCAR, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - 8/25--Emmy Awards, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - 8/25--Tater Tots, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - 8/26--Breast cancer, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - 8/27--Boodles/Jolly Time/Nostalgia, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - 8/29--McCauley Connor, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - 9/2--20 Questions, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - 9/2--New York City Marathon, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - 9/4--NFL, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - 9/8--MetLife, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - 9/9--Conde Nast Traveler, 2014 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - 9/10--MTV/Trojan condoms, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - 9/12--Esquire Mentor, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - 9/15--The Limited/Scandal (series), 2014 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - 9/15--Richmond (Va.) "Out RVA" LGBT campaign, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - 9/16--Google, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - 9/17--Andy Warhol/Absolut, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - 9/19--Belmond (Orient Express), 2014 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - 9/22--Special Olympics, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - 9/23--Lisa Sherman/Ad Council, 2014 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - 9/24--The CW Network 2014-2015 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - 9/25--The Good Lie, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - 9/29--Advertising Week, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - 9/29--In the Raw, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - 9/30--Advertising Week, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - 10/1--Advertising Week, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - 10/2--Advertising Week, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - 10/3--Diversity in advertising, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - 10/6--Advertising Week, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - 10/6--Jersey City, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - 10/9--Interbrand, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - 10/13--Renaissance Hotels, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - 10/14--CommonGround, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - 10/15--72 and Sunny/NY, 2014 (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - 10/16--Christmas, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - 10/17--ANA (Association of National Advertisers)/BMA (Business Marketing Association) merger, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - 10/20--Traditional medicinals, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - 10/20--Whole Foods, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - 10/21--OgilvyAmp, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - 10/22--Council of Public Relations Firms, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - 10/24--Nest/WeMo, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - 10/27--Morris the Cat, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - 10/29--Siegel Gale/Simplicity, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - 10/30--Christmas, 2014 (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - 10/30--Christmas, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - 10/31--Scripps Network/Veterans, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - 11/3--CNET, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - 11/3--Prudential Center, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - 11/5--Glenfiddich, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - 11/7--Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - 11/10--Car magazines/YouTube, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - 11/10--NBC/Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - 11/10--xBox, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - 11/12--CNN Films/VW, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - 11/13--American Airlines, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - 11/13--Design Network, 2014 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - 11/17--Revlon, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - 11/18--SS, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - 11/19--Pizza Hut, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - 11/20--Nikon, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - 11/21--E-cigarette conference, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - 11/21--Intel, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - 11/24--Sid Lee USA, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - 11/26--TCM/Disney, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - 12/1--20 Questions, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - 12/1--CBS/Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer 50th anniversary, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - 12/3--Targeting via mobile devices, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - 12/5--"Bold" brands, 2014 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - 12/8--3 Olives vodka (last issue of email newsletter), 2014 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - 12/8--Cosmopolitan/New Year's Eve, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - 12/9--UBS Media Conference, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - 12/10--Subaru, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Examples of releases and information used to write online newsletter, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Anheuser-Busch, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--Audi, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--Axe, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--Bank of America, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--Beats Music, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--CarMax, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Cheerios, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--Chevrolet, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Chobani, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--Chrysler, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--Coca-Cola, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--Dannon/Oikos, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--Doritos, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--Early coverage, 2014 (Box 191, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--Experts, polls, etc., 2014 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl--GoDaddy.com, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl--H, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl--Heinz Ketchup, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Intuit/Goldieblox, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Jaguar, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--Kia, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--M, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--Microsoft, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--Paramount, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--Pepsi, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Radio Shack, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--Sodastream, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Square Space, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--Subway, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--T-Mobile, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--Toyota, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--Turbo Tax, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--VW, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--WeatherTech, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 21)
    - Super Bowl--Wonderful Pistachios, 2014 (Box 192, Folder 22)
  - Ideas for Articles and Other Writings, 1980-2014 and undated; 10
    - 2014 forecast, 2013 (Box 192, Folder 23)
    - 9/11 notes, 2001 (Box 192, Folder 24)
    - Absenteeism, 2007 (Box 192, Folder 25)
    - Ad spending/forecasting, 1988-2008; 2 folders (Box 192, Folder 26-27)
    - Arm Hammer, 2013 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Attacking competitors, 2013 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Auntie Anne's mobile campaign, 2012 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - AXA gorilla, 2006 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Barilla, 2014 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Best and worst ads, 2006 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - BETC Start-up Lab, 2013 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Bewitched (movie), 2004 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Black and white images, 2011 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Canoe Ventures, 2009 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Characters, 2007 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Christmas story, 2006 (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Coca-Cola, 1989-2001; 4 folders (Box 193, Folder 13-16)
    - Coca-Cola, 1989-2001; 2 folders (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
    - Coke/Pepsi, 1993 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Detroit, 2013 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Dodge "Grab Life" campaign, 2007 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Ernie Kovacs, 2012 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - G2/Shopper Marketing, 2013 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - GlobalHue, 2013 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Hipsters, 2012 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - James Bond, 2012 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Juan Valdez, 2006 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Laskerville, 1991 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Long agency relationships, 1994-2001 (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Mad Mad World of Advertising/Delta Sky, 2010 (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-2004; 2 folders (Box 194, Folder 15-16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-2013; 2 folders (Box 195, Folder 1-2)
    - Mobile marketing, 2012 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Movie sneak peeks, 2011 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Nation Magazine/Native advertising, 2013 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - New Yorker, 1985 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Nostalgia in ads, 1995-2011; 2 folders (Box 195, Folder 7-8)
    - Old music in ads, 2007 and undated (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Olympics, 1988-2006; 2 folders (Box 195, Folder 10-11)
    - Omnicom/Publicis merger fail, 2013-2014 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Oscars/Academy Awards, 2004-2007 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Pan Am, 2011 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Pepsi, 1988-1993; 2 folders (Box 196, Folder 3-4)
    - Philips, 2006 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Phone numbers in ads, 1995-1996 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Piece of the Action, 2005-2007 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Powerful Yogurt, 2013 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Preppie, 2012 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Programmatic buying, 2012 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Reckitt Benckiser, 2013 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Retail ad spending, 2008; 2 folders (Box 196, Folder 12-13)
    - Screenvision, 2013 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Soft drinks, 1987-1998; 2 folders (Box 197, Folder 1-2)
    - Subaru, 2007 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl, 1988-2007; 3 folders (Box 197, Folder 4-6)
    - The More Things Change, 1980-1985 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Time/Pharmaceutical industry, 2012 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Value, 2012 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Vintage cars in ads, 2003-2004 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Reporter notebooks, 2012-2014; 5 folders (Box 198, Folder 1-5)
- Large-Format Materials, 1931-2014 and undated; 8
  - Advertisement--Absolut direct mail (Absolut Dad, Cozy), 1997, 2001 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Aflac, 2004 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--American Eagle Outfitters catalog, 1999 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Apple "Think Different", 1997 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Bitemenyc.com, undated (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Bloomingdale's catalog, 2008 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Booking.com folder, undated (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Burger King direct mail, undated (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Cadillac SRX, 2009 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Calvin Klein, 1995 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Coco Chanel, Tell Me a Tale of Coco pop-up book, undated (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Dirt Devil with Fred Astaire, 1995 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--Donna Karan catalog mailer, 2001 (Box OV1)
  - Advertisement--J. Peterman gift book with "Titanic" movie props and memorabilia, undated (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--JC Penney, Dear Closet Make Room, 2013 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Joe Camel, 1996 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Kellogg "Diversity Makes Us Strong", 2006 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Lucky Strike, 2000 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Miscellaneous ads from New Yorker, circa 1954 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Negro Baseball Leagues 75th anniversary including Wheaties box, 1989 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Orbitz "Visit Planet Earth," undated (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Paddles (Saveur, a face, Simpsons mask), 1995-2014 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Red Gold Tomatoes painted on silo, undated (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Saks Fifth Avenue, 1931, 2010 (Box OV2)